qupads.com 2016-11-08

# QupAds Privacy - QupAds

### Privacy

Effective on 1 August 2016

This Privacy Policy describes how QupAds, inc. (QupAds) collects and uses the personal data (included within the broader concept of “personal information” in this Policy) you provide on our website www.qupads.com. It also describes the choices available to you regarding our use of your personal information and how you can access and update this information.

1\. Collection and Use of Personal Data

2\. Information Sharing

2.1. Processing of Personal Data

2.2. PayPal, Payoneer or Payza

3\. Cookies and Other Tracking Technologies

4\. Security

5\. Additional Info

5.1. Correcting and Updating Your Personal Information

5.2. Links to Other Web sites

5.3. Notification of Privacy Statement Changes

6\. Contact Info

**1\. Collection and Use of Personal Data**

This Policy sets out the basis on which any personal data we collect from you, or that you provide to us, will be processed by us. Please read the following carefully to understand our views and practices regarding your personal data and how we will treat it.

We collect the following personal information from you: 

  * Contact Information such as name, email address, mailing address, phone number;

  * Billing Information such as credit card number, and billing address;

  * Financial Information such as bank account numbers;

  * Unique Identifiers such as user name, account number, password; and

  * Information about your business such as company name, company size, business type. 

As is true of most websites, we automatically gather information about your computer such as your IP address, browser type, referring/exit pages, and operating system. We use this information to:

  * Fulfill your order;

  * Send you an order confirmation;

  * Send you requested product or service information;

  * Send product updates;

  * Respond to customer service requests;

  * Administer your account;

  * Send you a newsletter;

  * Send you marketing communications;

  * Respond to your questions and concerns; and

  * Conduct research and analysis. 

**Choice/Opt-Out**

You may choose to stop receiving our newsletter or marketing emails by following the unsubscribe instructions included in these emails or you can contact us at _[privacy@qupads.com](mailto:privacy@qupads.com)_ for such purposes.

**2\. Information Sharing**

We will share your personal information with third parties only in the ways that are described in this Privacy Policy. Otherwise, we do not transfer or sell your personal information to third parties.

**2.1. Processing of Personal Data**

We may provide your personal data to companies that provide services to us, necessary for our business activities such as shipping your order, offering customer service, hosting services, mailing services and related. The following companies are authorized to use your personal information only as necessary to provide these services to us:

We may also disclose your personal information:

  * As required by law such as to comply with a subpoena, or similar legal process:

  * When we believe in good faith that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights, protect your safety or the safety of others, investigate fraud, or respond to a government or court request:

  * If QupAds is involved in a merger, acquisition, or sale of all or a portion of its assets, you will be notified via email and/or a prominent notice on our site of any change in ownership or uses of your personal information, as well as any choices you may have regarding your personal information: and

  * To any other third party with your prior consent to do so or following all applicable legal requirements depending on the case.

**2.2. PayPal, Payoneer**

If you choose to use PayPal, Payoneer to finalize and pay for your order, you will provide your credit card number, directly to PayPal/Payoneer. PayPal/Payoneer privacy policy will apply to the information you provide on the PayPal/Payoneer Web site.

**3\. Cookies and Other Tracking Technologies** ****

A cookie is a small text file that is stored on a user’s computer for record-keeping purposes. We use cookies on this site and have implemented and opt-in system so that users expressly consent to our use of cookies. We do not link the information we store in cookies to any personally identifiable information you submit while on our site.

We use both session ID cookies and persistent cookies. We use session cookies to make it easier for you to navigate our site. A session ID cookie expires when you close your browser. A persistent cookie remains on your hard drive for an extended period of time. You can remove persistent cookies by following directions provided in your Internet browser’s “help” file.

The use of cookies by our partners, affiliates, tracking utility company, service providers is not covered by our Privacy Policy. We do not have access or control over these cookies. Our partners, affiliates, tracking utility company, service providers use persistent cookies to make it easier for you to navigate our site.

Our Web site includes Widgets, such as AddThis, which are interactive mini-programs that run on our site to provide specific services from another company. Personal information, such as your email address, may be collected through the Widget. Cookies may also be set by the Widget to enable it to function properly. Information collected by this Widget is governed by the privacy policy of the company that created it.

**4\. Security**

When we collect personal information directly from you, we follow generally accepted industry standards such as SSL, to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore we cannot guarantee its absolute security. If you have any questions about security on our Web site, you can contact us at privacy@qupads.com.

**5\. Additional Policy Information**

**5.1. Correcting and Updating Your Personal Information**

To review, update, ensure it is accurate, or delete your personal information please contact us at privacy@qupads.com.

We will retain your information for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide our services to you or as applicable according to the law. Please contact us if you wish to cancel your account or request that we no longer use your information to provide you services. We will retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements.

**5.2. Links to Other Web sites**

Our site includes links to other Web sites whose privacy practices may differ from ours. If you submit personal information to any of those sites, your information is governed by their privacy statements. We encourage you to carefully read the privacy statement of any Web site you visit.

**5.3. Notification of Privacy Statement Changes**

We may update this privacy statement to reflect changes to our information practices. If we make any material changes we will notify you by email (sent to the e-mail address specified in your account) or by means of a notice on this site prior to the change becoming effective. We encourage you to periodically review this page for the latest information on our privacy practices.

**6\. Contact Information**

You can contact us by writing or emailing us at the address below:

Email: privacy@qupads.com
